Welcome everybody to another beyond
Bitcoin hangout where you can power
yourself up with your own tokens. Today
is Saturday September 30th 2017 and this
is hangout number 226. We are
still in the beta stages of Whaletank
hangout and Whaleshares so there will
be cool things that do come in the
future.
But as of present we have a couple cool
things already where we like to benefit
the individuals who have a little bit of
interest in creating their own tokens
and potentially leveraging them to help
their own projects. Every week people
join up to the whaletank to talk about
their projects provide updates in what
they're doing in the crypto space. And
hopefully they're also considering how
they can leverage the creation of the
token and the utilization thereof, to not
only empower their project but empower
the other people who want to hold those
tokens and leverage those tokens to help
the project as well. This is one of the
ways that I'm trying to incentivize
people to play around in the sandbox, use
these tokens, see what works, see what
doesn't and help us to document the
process and the progress or sometimes
the pitfalls. The entire story thereof.
Now with that said everybody who wants
to post a project can go to the weekly
RSVP threads at steemit.com forward
slash @officialfuzzy where I
post the RSVP hangouts, hangout threads and I
resteem other people's content.
And every week these
individuals who join up are allowed to
RSVP. We ask them to get upvotes from
people who are within the community  and outside of the community to
join up to do so as well. The reason
for this is it shows us that there are
people within the ecosystem who are
willing to upvote you and kind of step
in and say yes I backed this person. If you do not
back a person and you do not believe in
what they're doing
feel free to post and a reply, as opposed
to a flag, giving information on
what is going on with the
individual with the project at hand. And
if there's something that ends up being
important that we needed to know about I
will always gladly tip people who bring
relevant information in a productive
manner. Now with that said there are a
few cool things that we
offer with power-ups to people who do
create their own tokens and post the
link to where it trades on the Bitshares
DEX. If you have a token and you are
willing to distribute it to these
hangout attendees and also have it on
the Bitshares DeX, you are able to
double the chances of you becoming of
the first or increase the chances of
being in a preferable order, meaning the
first first second or third in these
hangout segments.
If you have a token holding this token and
posting the link to it will double your
chances as one powerup. As the second
powerup we have 15 minutes that are
established for every project to have as
a base. However you can earn extra
minutes by share dropping on the people
who are going to attend this hangout and
are going to sign the guest list that I
will provide. Now if the community is
interested in that share drop, and once a
part of that share drop say yes,
we can give you up to ten extra minutes
to talk about what is going on. I will
always consider
whether the community is wanting
to add extra minutes because of the
conversation too as well or just for the
tokens. But we will definitely be able to
offer you extra time if you want to
leverage those tokens. And finally we
give out well over five six hundred
dollars a week
this hangout alone.
Historically has actually been well over
a thousand dollars a week to the people
who participate. And there's nowhere else
that I know of that you can transparently do this in
the Steem ecosystem and earning these
tokens. So I urge everyone to consider
joining up because those people who do
have their own token and join up and
provide the link for the final powerup
that we offer, you will be able to
potentially earn one thousand beyondbits which is worth approximately four
hundred dollars at present. So with that
said at the end of every week whenever I
choose that person, if you believe that
your token is more valuable and that
there might be an opportunity that that
you think that I missed, you can always
reach out to me and talk to me about it
after the fact, and maybe maybe I will
change my mind. But if you do not have a
token that you're leveraging, you will
not be able to earn these thousand beyondbits. However I do take the amount that
is earned and I distribute it to the
people who join these hangouts as guest
speakers. So with that said if you would
like larger payouts consider trying to
get the whale tank hangouts uploaded
further! Tell people about them. Tell
people about your project and send a
link to the Whaleshares hangout. Do
what you can to promote us, because
promoting us and what we're doing here
is promoting everybody and also giving
us the resources to continue paying you.
Now with that said today the order of
precedence has been established. @Xanoxt
from Rudex, at six dollars and
seventeen cents.
Nutela, had some things that he was
going to talk about with Decent,
and he is standing at three
dollars and twenty seven cents. @asbonclz
is going to be talking about
addressing philippine problems monthly.
And that is hashtag
for better Philippines on Steemit. And
he is tied with @Nutela who will come
third. @Voiceshares a fitness sessions
we'll be following that and that will be
@rideofpassion. We will then follow
this by GS gaming. And we will cap off
the day with @theMarkyMark and his
project buildawale updates. So with
that said I thank everyone who has
joined up today and who join us every
week. And I thank you all for the little
things that you do that help us. All of
you offer incredible value. And all of
you offer unique value. So always try to
consider how you can leverage that to
help each other because that's how we
form synergy and create ridiculous
amounts of value. Now with that said
@Xanoxt I'll go ahead and I'll ask you
are you ready to step up to the plate
and give everybody an update on what's
going on in the Rudex ecosystem?
Okay @Xanoxt really quickly I can
give you about 20 more seconds if that's
okay? We're a little bit over the 15
minutes but you're more than welcome to
join up every week and give us a status
as well.
Thank @Xanoxt and if people want
to reach out to you guys and ask you any
questions, or heck maybe they know of a
chain or a graphene-based chain or
something similar like bitshares 1.0
based kind of chain, a graphene 1.0 chain.
How would they reach out to you and
contact you to let you know about all
this stuff?
Sounds good and thank you very much
everybody for joining up to these
hangouts and participating in them.
Thank you @Xanoxt for joining up to
provide all this information. You see
these are things that a lot of people do
not know about and they should. And this
is one of the means of us getting this
information out in a way that is open
and transparent. I just want to urge
everyone here, who is part of these and
those of you who are listening, to
consider,
we have 2500 listeners just on
soundcloud a week. So we have people out
there who are paying attention and
listening to us as well. If you're a
listener and or you're in
here, please conside if there's a
project that really seems like it's
going to bring value to your stake and
that you think that you can add value to
them and give them a little bit of help
in any way shape or form it, does not
have to be always money. This is the
space of disruption, the disruption comes
from creation and innovation. So innovate
and use your own value propositions to
uplift and support these valuable
projects. Because without these projects
we're kind of standing still in the
water. And it's really important. It's
really important to help them. And I know
that I don't always do it perfectly but
I will say this just always try if you
can. If there's a project that seems
valuable to you even if it's just one or
two minutes to share something every
week, it's something they might not
otherwise have.