Sure and I'd like to begin well you said
something about tokens and if you guys
know big Steem started as a translation
project for posts on Steem and for
all the things related to BtiShares, to
Steem [and] to Graphene technology in general.
And we were at some point I think it was
like last December or maybe January this
year [that] we're considering creating tokens
to sell translation things and with this
whole thing about community tokens we
might consider doing that actually but
it's something that I just wanted to say
for like kind of historical reasons.
We have a team of translators and we
have quite a bit of people who asked us
to translate things. When we started we were
thinking about how to monetize what we
are doing because you know most of
things we do we do for Steemit votes
and Golos votes. And sometimes they give
you nice payout and the translator is
happy because the money goes to the translators.
But sometimes not so much and we were
thinking about things that would allow
to have some sort of stable income.
But instead we went and start doing our
own interface for bitshares
and that also started as the translation
project. Because bitshares didn't have a
Russian interface at the time
and we were approached by testers who said
like "you guys are working on this maybe
you want to do Russian tools translation?"
We said yeah sure and then after we did
that we thought "okay we have this
interface translation we could probably
create our own interface and have a lot
of ideas about what we want to see on
bitshares". And that way we had an ability to
fullfill all of them. For example one of the
things that that we have that's
different from when BitShares started is our
telegram based trollbox that we
have a sandboxed iframe with the chat
blog?? A lot of people say that was
a security problem and we spent a lot of
time to safeguard this. At some point we
were considering maybe seeing if there's
code for chatbrel?? and working on our own [version] so
we would know that it's safe enough.
Because when you are dealing
with cryptowallets such as Bit-
Shares DEX essentially you can't have
too much security. Anyway one of the
things that we always wanted as a Ruble
MPA (Market Pegged Asset) and we created it and gave it
to the committee. So it's now an
official Ruble currency MPA of
BitShares
and all price
feeds for it are provided by
producing??witnesses. And also after that,
since we position ourselves as Graphene
ambassadors for russian-speaking
audience we also worked and talked
with communities of Peerplays, of Muse
, of Golos and of Steem and Bitshares
itself and created 0% marketfee
gateways that allow people to trade
their their tokens and exchange their
tokens from Graphene based networks
without any friction other than paying
miniscule Bitshares commissions. That
is made possible because we don't have
any investors that we
have any responsibilities [to] in turning a
profit and [things] like that. And also
[because] we have an active witness in
all those networks. In Bitshares we're a producing witness.
In Peerplays and in MUSE we're a producing
witness and in Steem and Golos we are
in the top 20 which is maybe one
or two percent ,or I don't know several
hundred thousand or like millions of
vests away from being a top 19 witness
and producing a block every round. But
even even without being there
we're still close to the top. On
Steem currently we've been running witness
since spring. I think it was late
March or early April when we
announced our the launch of our witness. We are still not in top 50 so if you
want to vote for a witness to support
whatever what we are doing, you'll have
to input the witness name in the field
for voting for non-in-the-top witnesses
and this name is "Blockchained" like
block chain ed. H opefully we
consider that most likely if enough
people vote for us we have to be made
like [rank] 30 and maybe eventually make it into the top. But top 30 would
be nice and I think it would be enough
to allow us to accelerate what
we're doing by quite a bit. Next up in the things that we are
planning to do:
we are currently tinkering with with the
Ethereum nodes. We have to run one to be able to gain?? ERC20 tokens and our
first ERC 20 token, once we have that
operational is going to be EOS and I'm
not sure on the particulars yet but most
likely will have a 0% market fee for
EOS token only because at some point
it's going to be a Graphene based token. And once
that's happened we'll create a gateway for EOS.
Because we think that having Bitshares as a premier platform for EOS tokens and
all the tokens created on EOS is
achievable and is actually
desirable because as far as I know there
are projects on creating DEXes on EOS
itself but we have the positioning to be
first such a DEX without actually
import?? to EOS because graphene chains
have an ability to sidechain to each
other and hopefully within the next half
a year so teams on EOS and other chains
would realize the tools to allow that
and do all the research required for
that. Next up we are probably going to
try and backport escrow functionality
from Steem into Bitshares. And we have a team of people who can work on that.
Possibly as soon as we are sure that
yeah that's feasible for us in a short term
will create a working proposal for that if
meirin?? beats?? us to that. Because escrow
functionality would allow creation of
peer to peer gating. So you will have
something along the lines of
local bitcoins. Except local bitcoins
are a centralized service that allows
peer to peer exchanges of bitcoins. [That said] we were researching using the multi-sig
schemes for that and decided that, while
it's possible it's still a bit clunky.
That's why we kind of shifted it some time into the
future. Once the tools that offer more
elegant solutions are in
place.That's probably all for now,
if you have any questions... Oh yeah,
another thing is; hopefully if you are
going to Steemfest you will be able to
see me if I get my visa done in a timely
manner. Because if that happens I'll
go to Steemfest and do a presentation
there. But I'll know in maybe a week or
week and a half.
Yeah we translated a lot of text
for them and we are planning to have a
Decent gateway also powered by being a
witness on Decent Network. But it's
probably going to be after an
ERC20 gateway. Since it's not that
hard to create gateways for
graphene-based
systems for us, it might happen before the ERC20 gateway but I'm not sure
on the timeline. But yeah that's in our plans and if you launch in
a Graphene based Network and you have a solid community and solid business case
for use of blockchain and are looking to
listed it we are open to providing
gateways to the DEX because as far as
we are concerned DEX is the thing that
tie all the Graphene based
chains together. And any other
chains as well. But we first look for
several things: one of them is; if the
blockchain in question has any sort of
governance solutions, so you can in the
future expect to see maybe Decred or I
don't know - DASH. The second
thing is privacy centric block chains
that's something that we really like. So
Monero, ZCash,
I don't know PIVX or well whatever, are
the chains that have
functionality we are looking into
creating but that's probably going to
be in 2018, maybe earlier. Our
idea is that we want to move at the pace
that's comfortable for us. So we are
sort of you know when done,
there are no ATA's but for Graphene based
chains it's maybe like we got to asses
about that, we got to to set up the
infrastructure for that and now that we
have, to test that and release into the
to the public. And then another couple of
weeks to do a public testing before we
send the code upstream. So it can be
included into the reference wallets and
into any other the Bitshares based
interfaces.
You'll still have to do it via Bitshares.
You send your money to for example
Decent gateway on Bitshares. You get Rudex decent tokens or
whatever they're going to be called. Then
you go and exchange them for, I don't
know Rudex tokens, and can then
send them to news network. And the thing
is since there are a 0% market fees
we're not actually taking any money from
from those trades. And since most
most graphene-based block chains don't
have sending or receiving fees or
transaction fees. We we have zero
transaction fees to send it this way or that. And even with Bitshares and Peer-
plays that have those transaction fees,
since we are getting paid by the
blockchain and the volume on on those
movements is offset by those payments so
we are able to afford that, there are
minimum amounts that we process. But
it's still it's still pretty
friction free frictionless for you if
you're sending money from one blockchain
to another. But it still requires
people willing to to trade. Well maybe
depending on how liquid the
market, is it may be best if you take your Decent tokens sell them
for Bitshares and then say buy MUSE tokens
for Bitshares but still [you have to exchange]. And yeah one of
the things that the community can help
us with is doing the... Yeah.
Yeah, okay no problem.
Yeah sure cool. So one of the things that
you can help us with is market making. If
you have a lot of tokens or one of those
chains, you are welcome to come and
provide the liquidity for them. Yeah. Also
vote for witnesses on all those networks.
We are looking for votes on Steem and
in the chat here there were details about
that. Yeah, thank you for having me.
Power?? You can leave comments on our
steem blog. You could also contact us our
own on telegram.
We have a really heavy presence on
telegram with several several groups for
all these Graphene chains. So we have Peer plays rooms??, EOS rooms,
we have Bitshares DEX rooms and
all of them.
Yeah I think yeah. In the chat here's
the links, the device posting them.