terrified
you
hey also can I say something about
buildawhale I mean @themarkymark is
amazing he's a great developer please
consider voting him for witness too I
know he's not going to say it but he's
doing great things
and the whole field of the nodes and
he's trying to work with a lot of these
guys getting things fixed he's helping a
lot of people do their stuff but he's
not getting this to recognize enough for
what he does
so if you guys please vote for him
for witness his servers running
pretty well he knows what he's doing
he's a good good person for us on
Steemit and just to show some
support
you
no that should be good forever
yeah that's the one that's on the
posts