@markymark you want to step up and chat
a little bit about the buildawhale
you
well I just wanted to say because of
this and I've been pretty pumped up
since I heard this since you told me what
was going on and that you've gotten to
this point and just because of
the progression so I'll just say if
anybody wants to go out and and kind of
show the progression through audio
parts from project BuildaWhalel on
soundcloud you can download them and
maybe I'll just post
something about it for like 300 beyondbit
reward or something to have people
posts kind of like let's get a
timeline auditive of audio clips for you
saying we have this much we have this
much we have this much you know maybe through in
a little song in the background
or something
@steempowerpics is pretty good man I'm
sure that he can do it
if you ask him but I will gladly pitch
in toward it men to be honest it for
something like that I think these are
the types of things that if the
community showcases them this is your
content right its
downloadable by everybody you can go out
and download it it's raw you can
edit it to do whatever you want except
obviously lie and make it sound like
MarkyMark put his words
together to say that he kills goats on
mountaintops and eats their eyeballs or something weird if you
do that if you do that we'll probably
come after you
but other than that definitely verified
but first he dragon breaths them right
but
you
really quick markymark I need to ask
you have you done
anything with the website yet or are
you getting started on that
you
well we actually have the reason I bring
this up is we have it's it's not
finished but it's in MVP form for a  front-end website
we're gonna make
it for US talk we're gonna have it too
so quite literally you'll have the
trending content from there that
you can actually kind of have a
news visualization for the forums right
so you might be out you don't want to go
looking at the forums on your cell phone
but you can go and check and see what
the news site looks like and what's
going on right and you can actually
break it down into various tags and you
know have a primary tag with subtags
underneath it and all the
things go there and the
reason why I bring this up is in the
current form you might see that there's
some tools that you have access to in
there there and some code that you can
utilize and I've paid for it
I meanI need more people to
probably work with it anyway and I don't
mind if people take it and just it was
supposed to be open source from the very
beginning I just got the guy who started
building it was a very fun story that
you guys can go listen to the archive of
at any point in time looking back on
it its actually quite funny but it
is available if you're interested in
checking it over man you just have to be
obviously stubbornly persistent to make
sure I get you in connection with the
guy
I believe
that it was meant to
be able to be a wordpress plugin
yeah
well that sounds like these two
things might marry together then pretty
well buddy
you
sounds good
I think
we talked a little about this art
together last night maybe it was gosh
I've been staying up so late doing stuff
the nights trail I think it was last
night that we talked but regarding the
full node that you're planning on
running for Steem
just make sure to let me know what you
need as far as how much it cost to run
and we can do that
at least until you get a witness you
know what I mean
anybody have any questions or comments we have about 3 minutes left
you
who makes steem watch
but you see that's the problem that I
have with that name I don't know if
that's serious or if it's like saying
actually like it like kind of like null
you
well it seems like 15 minutes went by
pretty dang quickly on this but I will
say Marky it made me
smile when you're like I'm a
250-thousand Steem power buildawhale is now a whale and I know and I
want to make this clear to everybody
because the Marky Mark the way he's
doing this is he's leasing steam power
so he's not doing this for his
own profit quite as much as he is to try
to make something that's extremely
valuable and intrinsically valuable and
putting money back into the pockets of
people who are doing things that are
bringing value so it's it's a very
important point I guess to bring up to
consider voting for him and I'll say
this he's watching you on steemwatch so
if to you vote him up he knows you
did buddy so anyway all jokes
aside how do they reach out to you Marky
Mark
you
good job man and these are the
types of things like whenever I'm
seeing what xanoxt is doing what voiceshares is doing Marky Mark  these guys
have been coming here for quite some
time now and to be able to to watch the
seeds as they're planted start growing
is probably one of the biggest blessings
that these hangouts have offered me
personally and I'll just say
these are the types of things that
rather than focus on television and all
the negative stuff that's going on maybe
just maybe we can leverage this type of
stuff what we're doing here to create a
new model that shows people that they
don't need to watch the negative shit on
television and that maybe they can
actually create their own stories and
archive their own stories the good and the
bad and show it truthfully honestly and
build value and prove it and show the
world that you can go through troubling
difficult times and still emerge
stronger and victorious so with that
said I appreciate everybody who joins
the whale tank and I look forward to
watching you all become whales