hey now it's going yeah
so for those who don't know buildawhale
is a bidding bot you send $0.50 SBD or
more we raised it because of things I'm
going to talk about and then we do a bid
or a vote down in about 2 hours and 40
minutes and that's how our cycle works
similar to a booster and all the other
ones
nothing new there and then we have human
curation at the back-end where we review
all the posts that come in there's about
a hundred plus a day it's getting to be
a lot more now and we review it we
pick 5 of them each day and we do a
daily digest and put that out on BuildaWhale
as well and then now we're doing a
contest in a weekend where on Saturdays
we announce the five best
curated articles for the week
picked from all the curators and then
the community can go and vote up and
pick which ones they think should win
and then the winners get WhaleShares
for winning that, theres a first, second
and third place for that, we
announced it yesterday and we're about
to announce the contenders for this week
the other thing I wanted announces we
now have 250,000 steem power so we are
now officially a whale and we're
dropping I think it's like 33 $34 votes
and it's going up as the seven-day
average of steem goes up so it will be in
a 35-40 range real soon
we also have a giveaway where anyone
that resteems our digest has an
opportunity of winning a free sponsored
curation and like we said before the
sponsored curation is you could pay
three steem to buildawhale and bypass
the entire queue and not have to be
curated through all the hundred plus
posts and you'd be featured right at the
top as a sponsored curation and as long
as it's not porn or anything unethical
we don't censor anything we just will
put you through
then we'll read it and give
you a human touch curation for that and
that's completely free if you win it
through one of our giveaways and then we
have some other things that have come up
that we're gonna be doing we're also
considering doing a website that will
feature the curated digested content and
feature it on a website that's outside of
steemi and that's most of what I have to
talk about that's public right now so
I'll open up the questions or if anyone
wants a chat about it
I'm sure @steempowerpics has already
started
thanks Nick appreciate that
thanks man appreciate that
no it's something I'm thinking about that
one of the problems is a canonical thing
is a duplicate content which becomes
very tricky because the whole advantage
would be for SEO reasons but Steemit
currently SEOs very well that's not
going to happen for long oh it's about
to get nerfed so putting on a separate
site wouldn't bring more traffic into Steemit the problem is it's a
canonical issue because now you have the
content of each one you have to delegate
which one is supposed to be the origin
of the content and you do that with a
Google canonical tag so I have to
figure out like which way it probably
wanted to do the site or something like
that so the traffic would come there
then go in or something like that I
haven't figured out but it was something
I was thinking about I'm not sure if I'm
going to do it because it does create
two things in there unless there was
another reason for the site to gain
traffic or have people on it it doesn't
serve a ton of purposes but I was just
thinking of ways of getting people
funneled into steam it
is it code or is it actually a
site that's going up
okay because that's where I would go,
WordPress, if I was gonna host it myself
because that's what I do
you know take a look at it, the other
thing I wanted to mention is I posted a
link earlier with some of the nodes
going on today
thanks for the witness @nutela I posted
an image of all the nodes that are down
right now and it's like 3 out of 5 are
gone right now and (preevix?) is fixing
things right now
so they they did support all the plugins
so they shut it down it's taking 6
to 12 hours to replay the blocks and I
still haven't seen an update of them
coming back online and I know a lot of
people use them like I was talking about
before how everything is centralized
with the witnesses in a full node, so I
was looking at doing it a full node that
would be public and I thought maybe we
could do a community one for Whaleshares
or something like that like Minnow
support did but I'm still thinking about
the technicalities of stuff like that,
right now I'm sitting on my second
witness so I have a failover and stuff
like that
I will do
the witness is about fifty two hundred
dollars for the hardware then you have
to maintain it which is interesting once
you get high enough like I'm getting
high enough where it's kind of expected
to have a backup and then you need to
double that and then you need to have
another server that basically can remote
kill switch them preferably 2 so
you're looking at two to four servers
when you start getting it to the range
that I'm in
and right now you need a 16-gig server
and that's growing fairly fast well you
can get away with a smaller one but it's
12-gigs right now so it pretty much has
16 gigs right now and it'll be breaking
that which means you'll have to get a 32
gig which brings the price up a bit
no but you're talking most likely
about a full node that requires 128 gigs
actually 104 but you're looking at
128-gig server and most
people that are doing it to go for a 256
gig server because 128 is not going to
last long so you're talking very limited
options when you start talking about
that calibre server because there's just
not many places that will host it, if you
do something like that like Rackspace
which is a triple-a hosting
company your looking over $1,000 yeah per
month and that's without any support or
redundancy or anything on that
there's absolutely no earnings for a
full node and that's what makes it suck
it's the most
expensive server you can rent 256 is
insane and there's no benefit to the
person hosting it there is no financial
reward or anything
because the way it was designed
what's not really smart for scaling
and they worked on trying to fix
that but
thanks for the witnessing @zone
yeah if you guys are wondering how I can
tell you who witness voted me like instantly
it's because I'm using a service called
steemwatch it will let you know if
somebody witness votes you and also let
you know if somebody unwitnessed votes
you and then it also will tell you if
you get notified in apost or
something like that, it has a few other
things like if someone posts or
something like that which it's kind of
buggy like setting it up once you have
the alerts set though it's good but
actually setting them up it takes a few
tries some times
I don't know I set it up a couple days
ago and I don't know who said it but I found
out about it from Tim clif but I was
building something similar that would
notify me through pushover about when
I change rank and so if somebody approves
me or something like that or I miss a
block or something like that
yeah it's the user void I guess I'd even
look at who made it I just started
checking out because Tim cliff said it
and he's pretty damn cool
it does work awesome though but it is really
really buggy like when you go and say
this is the first thing I want to
monitor it takes forever to do it, it takes
like four or five tries thanks Khan
Electric for the vote
discord and steemit chat are where I
usually hang out and I could post a link for
the discord for BuildaWhale but if you just tag me you'll find
me on most of the service
thanks Nick that's the unexpired one so
you just have to use it today
oh it is okay thought they had the same link
because I recognize the unexpirement
okay cool
you know we are looking at doubling the
steem power soon if this thing works out
but right now it's not a profitable
indenter we're trying to see if we could
at least make it so we don't have to
keep funneling fire into this thing to
keep it to the next week