always my friends
yeah if anybody has anything we need to
add this probably won't take 15 minutes
as I was just on you know a couple weeks
kind of discussing it but I just wanted
to kind of do an update regarding where
we're at and some of the things that
have changed thus far first off we've
been able to get with a really cool guy
@absord189 and he's able to
create banners intro videos anything
like that so if you guys are ever
needing anything like that go for the
@absord189 I would give my full backing
if you ever need anything like that so
yeah we've got a our official logo
we've actually had a few gaming
spotlights where we spotlight the
authors yeah check all post here
in a second
and then basically what we've decided to
do is in order to kind of push our
community forward is use the GS gaming
account, the steemit account as
spotlight account which basically allows
for any of the gaming members to post
from their personal accounts using the
GSG pictures and logos and
whatnot and thenh
either @BTCvenom or I will go through on
the GS gaming account and spotlight this
author and what it ends up doing is
goes through the week payout
and they receive all the SBD so we're
using it as a way to kind of help
authors and feel a little more loved
because we all know there's
quite the learning curve on Steemit so
I think we're at about 35
members now I think last week we were at
about eleven so it's a gonna take a
little time to get huge but I think it's
it's moving in the right direction so
we're always looking for more people to
come over and jump over I'll put the
discord link and
any links that I might have that might
be of importance I'll link sword 189
because he does some awesome work as
well thank you
yes sir
yep Delta
but yeah he does really good work
he's brand new to steemit so
wanted to make sure he gets a little
you know love from whoever the community
that chooses to use his services because
he does a really good job and
most of the stuff he's been just
wanting to do it out of the love of his
heart I have always been trying to send
him compensation and whatnot
but yeah he's a really good guy
anyways GetSetGaming is taking off
so I would be looking for it on the
steemit hot or trending here in the
next little while as far as for gaming
we brought on a few other people and
have been discussing with some possible
backers but we shall see I think it'll
just be one of those we grow as a
community and you know
"big payouts" come later for everybody
I'm doing what I can using personal
whale shares and whatnot to support the
authors through the GS gaming account so
anyways that is my kind of top up and
GetSetGaming news thank you guys
yeah the old snts yeah I
think ideally I would love to do
something like that I personally don't
know how to do that but if you have
somebody that you could link me with I
would be extremely interested for that
as well as I think steemits got talent
that it could use from that as well also
awesome I'll reach out to p.m. here
sometime today then I know you're busy
busy busy
the other thing I wanted to just briefly
announce was yes @steempowerpics
read my mind we've actually
been in discussion with Chris  of solar coach TopSol and he's
actually decided to give up five hundred
topsol a week to the winner of Steemits
got talent so that'll be another
especially going into the
eliminations here in the next few weeks
I think it'll be a nice way to bump up
prizes and whatnot for the elimination
people
yeah that would be awesome
definitely do you happen I don't even
think I have the a discord for peer
plays you have anybody I might be able
to contact or I'll just reach out in
p.m.
okay awesome I do have telegram so I'll
look around there but yeah I'll try and
get in touch with one of them and you
know if I could make a discord for him
that would be awesome too
yeah that's what I thought
awesome awesome
as far as the GS gaming I will put down
my discord port the community discord
but I'm basically as fuzzy will probably
vouch I'm always on discord I kind of
jump on steemit.chat here and there you
know a couple times a day just to check
but discord is my main bread and butter
I'm there pretty much 24/7 so that would
be the easiest way to meet me find me
yes sir
sounds good I'm all about helping
anybody I can
a top-class so anybody who wants to take
over this five minutes feel free
yeah I was kind of doing the similar
thing that you're doing I was kind of
reaching out to the community that just
kind of compiled
you know a general consensus of at least
the people that I reach out and follow
or who follow me I wanted to get kind of
their general consensus as far as what I
think I mean I think it's a cool way to
get around you know the whole ICO
situation that's going on right now but
on the flip side I think it's something
that's more or less already been done
you know whaleshares that kind of a
thing similar but different so I think
it'll be interesting I think it's going
to initially be a whole flood of
"BS" that everyone's going
to kind of have to go through because I didn't read the
entire white paper but I don't know
what system they're using to
you know "vent through the
BS" and the scam tokens and whatnot
I don't know if it's just going to be
whoever makes one can enter it and use
steemit as the ICO platform but I think
only time will tell
as we've seen the steemit
community issues pop up and there's
people that necessarily don't
Use Steemit the platform for what it's
for but I think the community does a
really good job of you know weeding
out the BS and then really getting down
to the the good core community you know
people who really care about steemit so
I think it's going to be a similar event
with these ICOS I think
initially it's just gonna flood the
market and then everyone's gonna have to
kind of okay this is the one to go to
this is not you know like that
no nobody wants to listen to you
damn toilet flexors
Roger that sounds great to me man
I appreciate it I'm already in the
telegram talking to go to play guys or
trying to they're in there in
some serious discussions going on right
now buy sell hold
yeah they're talking about something
else helmbet something
not quite sure what it even is
sounds good