well I was just  wondering
SMT tokens how you see it and
because you wrote a post about it I just
read it so maybe we can talk about that
the the best thing would be if we
could use steem like a form of discuss
with the queue you know with like a
common system because the reputation
could really help to leave the spammers
out and filter  the
good commands but I don't know
if it's like for data I just saw
some idea about it and which is
very good you know I I haven't read the
white paper also so
so yeah if they can make it more easy to
use I think. you know making
accounts on bitshares and doing this all
and watching the video of Kronos and I mean
it's not hard but yeah I don't know if
they can make it easier then all
the better but on the other hand maybe
if they make it too easy then you get
all this shit coins time will tell.