I've noticed that you are also
a busy guy on there so go ahead and feel
free to step up let everybody know give
your 15 minute presentation and we can
move forward
and that is @Zord189
as in Delta
sure have you ever thought about the
potential of tokenification for gaming
for this kind of group like
creating a community token well it's
it's I think a steem media token is what
they're going to call them when they
come out but we have tokens that can be
used for that up until then
well that's one of the things
I'll help you with if you need just so
you know
this is some cool stuff
but I think that the the gaming segment
that sector in general there's just so
much you can do in it so it's gonna be
cool to see where you're going with it
and I'll also remind you that there is
another chain another delegated people
stakechain called peer plays
some of the people who were
behind bitshares work with it and they
are going to be having it used just for
games and gamification and things like
that and I believe
they're going to have a unit a unity API
so I just want to let you guys know it's cheaper than when
I bought it so you guys can get it
cheaper than I bought it and I know that
they're doing stuff behind the scenes
from what they've told
me anyway and they've came out and
they've been pretty open about
joining the whale tanks in the past to
talk about it too so the only reason I
bring that up is you're in this perfect
spot where you're on steemit you could
make money and earn money and build a
community there and you can also create
kind of a synergy between steemit and
peer plays with that right
so yeah I mean if we can use these tools
to make more money on more platforms
like kind of how I tell @nutela
hey feel free to put all of our stuff
from the cent and if you want to kick me
some of the funds that you were in cool
if you don't that's fine too but you
leverage it and and earn on decent you
know what I mean that's another platform
that you guys like and it's based on
delegated proof of stakes so you know
it's gonna scale you know it's not gonna
have a bunch of people who want to use
it and then they're gonna go shit I
can't use it
so maybe just something to think about
for you
if you want to you could probably create
the discord yourself because I don't
think they have a discord they have a
telegram though
there you go apple crisp
well they are looking for people to get
witnesses and I mean it's
just it's just too good to be true that
you can earn from all these chains and
yeah it's called Voltron BamBam
and if you do it I
think that you'll be very happy
that you helped to build Voltron
or Ultron is my manager Mike wants to
keep saying so if anybody wants to reach
out to you how do they do so if they
want to help out or work with you in
some way shape or form with this project
could you provide the link in here for
the for the people who are joining up
today
that'd be awesome just so they have
access to to see what you're up to and
you never know when you
start looking at these various other
chains in it you can potentially make
some cash on all those you start being
able to potentially help people who join
up and become part of the community
maybe some of the people here will be
some of those people
does anybody have any questions or
comments before we close this segment up
we have five minutes left
my big thing is if you have a
coin that it cannot really
give people an opportunity to govern
their community or have some
semblance of structure that they can
leverage to get things
done that's one of the biggest things
that coins are gonna have
to deal with that and scalability if
you've got those two things as a coin
your community is going to be able to
survive through the hard times and you
will find those core people but I think
over time you guys might see that if
for instance some of these other texts
out there if they don't scale and
the only thing that they offer is "you
don't like it sell your coin" I think that's
going to be the mark of what's
going to make a shit coin a true shit
coin because if we're thinking about
cryptocurrency is something that's going
to empower people and it doesn't empower
people other than to buy the coin and
hold it and spend it and be a nice
little servant who doesn't ask questions
what happens with it or to be
able to be a citizen who has a say kind
of like and delegated proof of stake I
think there's a big big difference and
especially for longevity of coins and
the communities
especially for the toilet flushing
people the people who live their lives
around the toilets
okay well real quick before  we
head out I just want to thank you
BamBam808 and just to let everybody
know that is @gsgaming on Steemit and
thank you for joining up please feel
free to join up any  time and remind
me that man I'll do it
today with you I can make a token in
probably about twenty minutes during the after party if that's cool
sounds good
hmm well give him a reason to hold man
tell them all your ideas that's that's
the best thing to combat the FUD
well you'll figure it out and we'll talk
about probably the next time you
join up sound good
alright sounds wonderful